Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
世界波に乗ろう 力合わせて
ときめく方へ急ごう 始まりの合図
今こそ船出の時 光を上げたら
七色の風を切り 冒険の海へ
傷だらけの旅だけど 大事なものがそこにある
臨時ならいつだって 僕が守るから
大丈夫さ 前に進もう
太陽をいつも胸に
嵐が来たら肩組んで
その滝の光を見よう
夢の欠片集まれば
明日に向かう地図になる
だから同じ旗のもと 願いをつかわえようよ
僕らはひとつわき
S.T.R.P. 日本に recursがおっしゃない
新しい Sport
Well, I'm not mistaken, am I?
Gates of Justice
新宿りました
judicial island. But that's a lie. The court they have there is only for show. The truth is, if you've
been taken there, then you're already considered guilty. When you arrive, the government walks you
through an empty courtroom, leading to a pair of cold steel doors that tower above the entire island.
Those doors are known as the gates of justice. The criminals who walk through them must abandon
all hope. Once they reach the other side, they'll never see the light of day again. Once you set sail
beyond those doors, there are only two destinations you can reach, neither of which you are ever likely
to leave. One is Navy Headquarters, where the strongest military powers in the world gather
in the name of justice. The other is Impel Down, an underwater prison filled with torture chambers
and execution blocks. No matter how vicious they may be, the criminals imprisoned there can only
wait for death. In other words, going to Innie's lobby is no different than a death sentence.
There's no trial, no justice, and no hope of escape. Am I right?
Robin has a bounty on her head. No matter where they take her, she'll face death or worse.
Every second we sit here talking, she gets one step closer to the gates of justice.
Don't you dare tell us to wait until tomorrow!
If you know that much already, I've only got one thing to say.
Even if the sea was calm and you were able to set sail, that's the last place you should ever go.
Don't forget, you people are wanted criminals just the same as your friend.
Just like you said, Innie's lobby is the front door to the world government's own personal playground.
They've drawn battle lines around that place that should never, ever be crossed.
Regardless of how they feel about their crewmates, no pirate would be stupid enough to launch a rescue mission there.
They know what would happen.
Picking a fight in that place is like declaring war on the entire Navy!
Hey, I know how you must feel, but Pauly's right!
You can't leave during Aqua Laguna anyway!
You'll be dead before you even get there!
There's no point in throwing your lives away over this!
Luffy?
Find them!
We'll steal the ship!
Don't try to get in our way!
We're leaving now!
Whoa!
Even the waves got bad!
Is he gonna fight us?
That sure was scary!
Fine, then.
You wanna fight, you got it!
All of you!
Stop it!
Kokoro?
Stop being such a damn fool, Straw Hat!
Like it or not, Pauly's right on this one.
Shut up, Granny!
It's none of your business!
You sure about that, boy?
Either way, spokes are just trying to stop you from killing yourself.
The point is, no matter how mad you are, no ship can handle Aqua Laguna.
Only a sea train made by a legendary man stands a chance.
I know that, but I don't have any choice, since the only sea train in the world has left town already!
If you're prepared to die, then that's fine, just come along with me, we'll brave the storm on my sea train!
Who's that guy?
I don't know.
You idiots!
Don't just stand there!
If he's not wearing a uniform, then he must be an intruder!
Get him!
I guess playing innocent doesn't work in here.
And here I thought I could get out of a fight.
Oh well, it's not my funeral.
Sanji?
Hold it!
You think we're going to let you get away with that?
If you're smart.
Ah!
Okay!
Rats!
Wait, you didn't hijack the sea train just to rescue me, did you?
I don't even know what you're doing here.
Also, what's your name again?
I don't believe we've actually met before, have we?
Are you kidding me, you jerk?
Bingo!
Transponder snails!
Okay, this must be a communications room or something.
Lucky I ran into this place so soon.
Those guys I beat up in the last card only had a bunch of useless crap masks and costumes and stuff.
Anyway, now that I have this, I can get in touch with Nami!
Let me guess, he's one of your pirate friends, isn't he?
Ex-friend.
The question is, who are you?
I'm the face of Water 7's underworld.
The ship dismantler, Frankie.
So you're the bastard who beat up Usopp, huh?
He may be dead to me now, but he was part of our crew back then.
How many pieces do you want me to cut you into?
No, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
It's not like that now.
A lot of stuff's changed since then.
Hey, punk!
You're lucky I'm tied up!
Come on, man.
That line's getting old.
Seriously, he's a good guy.
He saved the Mary, at least for a while.
Oh, yeah.
The Mary was...
Whoa!
Come on, buddy.
You can't get all sad and mopey on me now.
Hey, Blondie, untie me!
Pretty please!
You can spend the rest of your life in that potato sack for all I care.
Screw you!
I said pretty please.
What the hell else do you want?
Stop it!
No more fighting, guys!
Look, if we keep yelling, then the Marines are gonna go!
Yeah, then shut up!
Say what?
They should have gagged both of you!
Yeah, whatever!
Just a time of your...
No fighting already!
Uh, Captain T-Bone, what are you...
Frankie's with them, too?
Yes, sir.
But I'm afraid that the C-Train has already departed.
Pauly and the other guys are out looking for Straw Hat and his friends.
But no luck.
Now that we all know that Robin needs saving,
then there's no limit to what we can accomplish.
Whoa!
A secret base?
It's been more than eight years since anyone set foot in here.
And nobody's touched the C-Train for more than 12.
Let's go, Chopper!
Right!
I'm warning you, the thing may not run anymore.
What?
You better be kidding me!
Now, now, settle down, boys.
You can run as fast as you like,
but you're not getting inside without the key.
Huh?
Now that's weird.
It's open!
Whoa!
Awesome!
Check out the face!
So cool!
Unlike the puffing tom, this one here's a crazy train.
Its name is Rocket Man.
Comes with no guarantees, so board at your own risk.
Rocket Man!
Sounds fast!
Neato!
Did you have to add the face?
Don't worry, it may be mean, but it won't bite.
Hey, look!
It's Ice Pops!
Hello there, Straw Hat.
So, you're okay after all.
It seems your friend's faith was well-founded.
I assume you brought them here, Kokoro?
The question is, what are you doing here?
You've been through a lot today.
You need rest.
Well, let's just say you and I were thinking the same thing.
We have a soft spot for idiots, don't we?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Go ahead.
I just finished servicing it.
Water and coal have been loaded and the steam's building up now.
Ha ha ha!
Thanks for getting it ready for us!
We owe you one!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Hmm.
I wouldn't celebrate yet if I were you.
You might not even survive the ride.
This was our failed prototype before we made the Puffing Tom.
No matter how you tune it, you can't control its speed.
In other words, it's a runaway train.
That's fine.
It can go as fast as it wants.
Hmph.
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Get on already!
We're leaving as soon as Nami gets here, Granny!
Oh, man!
Luffy, are you okay?
You've been kind of shaky on your feet since we found you.
He probably just lost too much blood.
Ugh, maybe.
I am feeling kind of dizzy.
I think I need some meat.
Hurry, this way!
Wait!
I don't see why you have to go all the way down here just to eat your dinner!
That's right!
If you're hungry, eat now!
You think all that food is for me?
What?
Sorry I took so long!
Nami.
Hey!
Save the small talk for later!
Get on board so we can go!
Wow, amazing.
So there's another sea train, huh?
He was hiding here all this time and we never knew.
This is a real surprise!
You're the one who told us we have to hurry!
Why are you the last one to get here?
And what's with the big bag?
I brought you food and drinks!
I'm sorry I just yelled at you!
He's ready to go!
You'll shoot out of the canal into the ocean.
If you can latch onto the railway after that, it should be a good start.
Don't you worry a bit.
I like to drink, but I take my job seriously.
You just stay here and give that body of yours a good rest.
Sounds fine to me.
And while I'm taking care of these pirate folk, I hope you don't mind watching Gonby and Jimny for me.
Yes, that's fine.
Don't go troubling yourself over him, either.
That boy got hit by a sea train, you know.
If he can survive that, I'm sure he'll be okay.
Besides, we've got the king of the pirates on our side.
We can't lose.
Huh?
Strawheads!
Who's there?
The Frankie family!
We're kind of busy right now.
Please, Straw Hat!
You guys gotta take us!
夢見た僕らは間違いじゃないと信じて 荒く埋める海原を渡って行ける
誰よりも浮かんで 思いやりもあるけれど
もしも君がこの船を降りて 違う世界にいたとしても
最後にはきっと笑えるよ
小輔りと予建何を報われ
カミクランはこっちのことを用意して 見舞い主に
が dellarenネジ ViolSシファリカも には、 atravésのトレ шヴaidバスの
フレッキィ様 meinem、頑張りGavin eVotix Mu uncle
みんなおりとりおじらごたえっと一緒にイベント
きどんどんどん性がどんいくり
いくんどんどんどんなお部さんに対して
một人をうが adjustで あなんて
な weetすぎるよ
そして、ワンピシスの仕上を介して
この次の効果から情報を狙う
ヒットファーキの者からです
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!